discreet-romance.com 2008-12-17

# Privacy Policies - Discreet Romance Adult Sex Toys Store

[](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.discreet-romance.com&sealid=101) TEG, LLC is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Web site [www.discreet-romance.com]. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Michelle White at privacy@discreet-romance.com. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily address, you should contact TRUSTe at http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

**Privacy Policy Coverage**  
The following privacy policy covers TEG LLC operated www.discreet-romance.com only 

**Information Collection and Use**  
Discreet-Romance.com will not share, sell or rent this information to others in any way other than as disclosed in this policy or stated at the point where the information is collected. Discreet-Romance.com collects information from our users in several areas of our Web site as described in this privacy policy. 

**Order Forms and Account Creation Forms**  
We request information from you on our order form and account creation form, including your contact information (such as name, email and shipping address) and financial information (order form only) (such as credit card number and expiration date). This information is used to fill your orders and for billing and shipping purposes. If we have trouble processing your order, we may use this contact information to get in touch with you. We share this information, and only that information that we believe is necessary, with those third parties that are involved in the processing of your order. For example, the financial institution that issued your credit card, and the shipping carrier that delivers your order. 

Third Party:  
When you order from our store, we will share your billing name, billing address, shipping address, credit card information as necessary for the financial institution to provide their service. 

Note: We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

**Updating of Personal Information**  
If your personally identifiable information changes, you may correct or update your information by login to your account through the login page and making the change on your account information page, or by emailing our Customer Support at sales [at] discreet-romance.com.   
If you wish to remove your account from our store, please contact us by emailing our Customer Support at sales [at] discreet-romance.com.   
See Contact Us below for more contact details 

**Credit Cards**  
We do not and will not store your credit card in our database. It is discarded the moment your card is authorized. 

**Emailing & Promotions**  

  * Discreet-romance.com will **NEVER** send out spaming or promotional emails to your account.
  * We will **NOT** send flyers or catalogs to your address.
  * The only time we will email you is regarding your order information or reply to your requests and inquiries.

**Session ID**  
Upon visiting our site, we assign you a unique Session ID and attempt to store that onto your computer in the form of a cookie. This is used to keep track of your shopping basket during your visit and between visits. 

**Tracking Service**  
Our website's tracking service is used only to monitor traffic, page views, and referral trends. No personal information is collected through this tracking service. 

**Security**  
We want to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information on our Web site, we take commercially reasonable steps to protect your information online and off-line. 

When you provide sensitive information on our site (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and protected with encryption software while in transit. While you are on a secure page, such as our order form page, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked. 

While we use encryption software to protect sensitive information online, we also use our best efforts to protect your information off-line. Access to all of our users' information is restricted in our offices. We take reasonable steps to ensure that only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. The servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment behind a locked cage. 

We utilize industry standard SSL encryption when accepting your credit card information during our online checkout process. In addition, we utilize the same encryption standard when transferring your credit card data to our internal fulfillment system. To further enhance our security measures, our fulfillment system is protected from access via the Internet and we we never store your actual credit card information. 

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of the other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy or email practices, we will post a link to those changes on our Home Page so you will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by e-mail. You will have the choice to allow us to use the information in this different manner. We will use information according to the privacy policy posted at the time the information was collected, unless you agree otherwise. 

**Special Note for International Users**  
By visiting our Web site and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that your personal information may be processed for the purposes identified in our Privacy Policy. In addition, such data may be stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction which may have less stringent privacy practices than your own. By providing us with your data, you consent to the transfer of such data. 

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, wish to have information about you deleted, opt-out of mailings, or want to place an order via a method other than the Internet, you can click [here](http://www.discreet-romance.com/contact_us.php) to contact us, or email us at privacy [at] discreet-romance.com. 

Privacy Statement last updated on: November 16th, 2006
